# **Felixnando Meraz**

# **Student - Mesa Community College**

Santan, AZ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Felixnando-Meraz/efedd59f8db1ca8b

I am currently working towards a Bachelor's in Electrical Engineering. I would like to have the opportunity to use the knowledge that I've learned in classes and through work experiences to apply them in a job related to my field of education. I am willing to learn new things outside of my field of degree to extend my knowledge and gain experience in a different area.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Student

Mesa Community College - August 2013 to Present

In class experience in; Matlab, C++, Chemistry/lab experience, Microsoft office word, excel and PowerPoint.

#### Worker

Meraz Woodwork - May 2011 to August 2015

Use of power tools such as, table saw, band saw, jig saw, circle saw, router, drill, air compressor, compressor nail guns and compressor spray painting.

> Taking measurements, estimating cost of cabinets/furniture, cutting wood, building cabinets/furniture, installing cabinets, delivering furniture.

#### Worker

New Structure Building - May 2009 to August 2011

Use of power tools such as wet tile cutter and drill, Installing tile, backsplash, pavers, ceiling tiles, drywall and some electrical work.

### **EDUCATION**

Mesa Community College 2019

Poston Butte High School May 2012

#### **SKILLS**

C++ (3 years), MATLAB (3 years), MICROSOFT OFFICE (3 years), MS OFFICE (3 years), AUTOCAD (Less than 1 year)

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## Skills

- > Bilingual
- > Coachable
- > Fast learner
- > Well organized

- ➤ Microsoft Office
- ➤ Carpentry
- ➤ Team player
- ➤ Knowledge in Matlab, C++ and AutoCAD